[{"id":"6188","question":"<p>His ________ attitude is the root cause of most of his problems.&nbsp;<\/p>\r\n","option1":"Inflexible ","option2":"Positive ","option3":"Incapable ","option4":"Innovative ","option5":"Playful ","correct_option":"Inflexible ","qa_date":"2016-04-23 04:48:19","section_description":"","max_marks":"1","answer":""},{"id":"6191","question":"<p>When he _________ that his life was in danger he called out for help.&nbsp;<\/p>\r\n","option1":"Feels","option2":"Decided","option3":"Forecast-ed ","option4":"Narrated ","option5":"Realized","correct_option":"Realized","qa_date":"2016-04-23 04:48:19","section_description":"","max_marks":"1","answer":""},{"id":"6193","question":"<p>Although he is a balanced person. He occasionally loses his ________.<\/p>\r\n","option1":"Power ","option2":"Grief","option3":"Temper","option4":"Anxiety","option5":"Wealth","correct_option":"Temper","qa_date":"2016-04-23 04:48:19","section_description":"","max_marks":"1","answer":""},{"id":"6194","question":"<p>The tunnel was so _______ and congested that we become frightened.&nbsp;<\/p>\r\n","option1":"Long","option2":"Broad","option3":"Dark","option4":"Quiet","option5":"Grief","correct_option":"Dark","qa_date":"2016-04-23 04:48:19","section_description":"","max_marks":"1","answer":""},{"id":"6187","question":"<p>For such a __________ task, there should be some special task force.<\/p>\r\n","option1":"Trivial","option2":"Gigantic","option3":"Definite","option4":"Simple","option5":"Complexity","correct_option":"Gigantic","qa_date":"2016-04-23 04:48:19","section_description":"","max_marks":"1","answer":""},{"id":"6192","question":"<p>Our country is committed to ________ peace all over the world.&nbsp;<\/p>\r\n","option1":"Starting ","option2":"Establishment  ","option3":"Maintaining ","option4":"Encompassing","option5":"Settle","correct_option":"Maintaining ","qa_date":"2016-04-23 04:48:19","section_description":"","max_marks":"1","answer":""},{"id":"6190","question":"<p>I do not approve __________ the views expressed by you.&nbsp;<\/p>\r\n","option1":"Wrote","option2":"Of ","option3":"At","option4":"For","option5":"Realized","correct_option":"Of ","qa_date":"2016-04-23 04:48:19","section_description":"","max_marks":"1","answer":""},{"id":"6189","question":"<p>If you _______ yourself with the culture of that area, you will be able to enjoy life there.&nbsp;<\/p>\r\n","option1":"Know ","option2":"See","option3":"Familiarize","option4":"Imbibe","option5":"Inculcate","correct_option":"Familiarize","qa_date":"2016-04-23 04:48:19","section_description":"","max_marks":"1","answer":""},{"id":"6186","question":"<p>We should involve all our colleagues in ________ important decisions.&nbsp;<\/p>\r\n","option1":"Instigating ","option2":"Deciding ","option3":"Pioneering ","option4":"Making","option5":"Identifying","correct_option":"Making","qa_date":"2016-04-23 04:48:19","section_description":"","max_marks":"1","answer":""},{"id":"6185","question":"<p>Proud people often look down ________ others.&nbsp;<\/p>\r\n","option1":"On ","option2":"for","option3":"at","option4":"upon","option5":"towards","correct_option":"upon","qa_date":"2016-04-23 04:48:19","section_description":"","max_marks":"1","answer":""}]